Let's get the show on the road.
我们开始吧.
Camera,and action.
摄像机,开始!
Hello. I'm Nina Barrett,
Hello. 我是Nina Barrett,
Director of Functions here at the Sheraton Boston.
事务部的主管,在Sheraton Boston.
To plan the perfect event,
要筹划一次圆满的活动,
there are a couple of things you should keep in mind.
有几件事请您牢记.
Cut. Let's go again.
停. 我们再来一次.
A good hotel should be able to...
一家好的饭店需要能够...
Cut,and action.
减掉, 开始.
A good hotel should be able to
一家好的饭店需要能够
plan around your needs and should stay within your budget.
按照您的需求来制定计划.而且不超出您的预算.
To make the best use of time and money,
而为了充分利用您的时间和金钱,
you should have a clear idea of what you want.
您必须清楚自己需要什么.
Oh...
Most important of all,
最重要的是,
you can expect the best from us and you shouldn't worry.
您将在这里得到我们最好的服务,无需操心
Cut. Nice job,Nina.
减掉. 干得不错, Nina.
I should never go in front of a camera.
我真不该到摄像头前的.